本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多美剧字幕 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
《反恐24小时》前情提要
Previously on 24
我是梅瑞狄斯·里德
This is Meredith Reed.
里德小姐
Ms. Reed,
那些你认为该对哈桑总统的死负责的人
the people that you think are responsible for killing President Hassan
他们不是单打独斗
were not working alone.
他们得到俄当局内部人士的资助
They were being funded and managed by people working
并受他们操纵
inside the Russian government.
你怎么知道的
How do you know this?
我被人陷害了  就像你昨天一样
I'm being set up, just like you were yesterday.
我得把这证据交给你
I need to get this evidence to you.
阿洛从国安局梯队情报系统获得了一份监听报告
Arlo got a cell phone intercept report off NSA's Echelon.
关键词是"杰克·鲍尔"
Key words: "Jack Bauer."
我们确定了声纹
We confirmed the voiceprint.
以里德与哈桑的关系
Reed's connection to Hassan means
她打心眼里愿意帮助杰克
she'd be highly motivated to help him.
他下一步棋就是把证据送媒体曝光
Take it to the press. That's his next move.
这是一个扫除一切障碍的大好时机  长官
This is a major opportunity to make everything go away, sir.
鲍尔和证据
Bauer and the evidence.
我得找到杰克
I need to find Jack...
不然他们会杀了他
or else they're gonna kill him.
如果我们能找到他
If we can get to him,
我们就能揭穿这个掩盖真相的阴谋
we can expose the cover-up.
-杰克一定有个帮手  -谁
- Jack's gotta be working with someone.  - Who?
我不知道  我没见过他
I don't know. I never saw 'em,
但从杰克配备有最尖端的武器和通讯系统判断
but Jack showed up with state-of-the-art weapons and comms.
帕维尔  发现鲍尔了吗
Pavel, do you see Bauer?
有机会就开枪
If you have a shot, take it.
我看见他了
I've got him.
把枪放下
Put it down.
上面都处理好了  杰克
Everything's all clear up on top, Jack.
跟我走  照我说的做
Come with me. Do exactly what I say.
走
Move!
他早知道这是个陷阱
He knew it was a trap.
证据在这张记忆卡里
The evidence is on this memory card.
拿着
Take it.
你一看到视频就知道一切是真的
When you see it, you'll know it's real.
刺杀哈桑的行动已万事俱备
The hit on Hassan is all arranged.
巴扎耶夫及其手下正在处理一切
Bazhaev and his people are taking care of everything.
我已知道是你杀了蕾妮·沃克
I already know that you killed Renee Walker.
我现在要知道的是俄罗斯政府里面
What I want to know is the name of the Russian pig
那头下命令的俄国猪的名字
inside your government that gave the order.
你的手机SIM卡在哪里
Where's the SIM card for your phone?
你这蠢货  你吞了下去
You dumb bastard, you swallowed it.
这一下是为了我的朋友
This is for my friend.
翻译： 化石鱼    罗玉凤    插线    hodala    wdjmhs    我是无辜的
■
时间轴：何何     校对：何何    罗玉凤    我是无辜的    aiai
您所拨打的是查尔斯·罗根总统的移动电话
You've reached the mobile number of President Charles Logan.
以下事件发生于下午一点到两点间
The following takes place between 1:00 P.M. and 2:00 P.M.
后期：冰河     特别鸣谢：咖啡   Nil    监制：何何
■
作为参与开创这一
As a principal player in this
史无前例和平盛事的重要一员
unprecedented and historic peace initiative,
国务卿卡宁出于健康原因
Secretary of State Kanin's untimely decision
不得不放弃参加协议签署
to withdrew for health reasons was a difficult one.
然而  总统希望大家知道
However, the president wishes it to be known
鉴于国务卿卡宁已离开以及罗根的毛遂自荐
that in Secretary Kanin's absence and per his own recommendation,
已由前总统查尔斯·罗根担任总统顾问
she has sought and gained the counsel of former President Charles Logan.
此时  总统很清楚
Now, the president is acutely aware
此项决定会引起一些争议
that this decision bears some controversy.
但罗根总统在外交政策方面的经验
But President Logan's experience with foreign policy
以及谈判的技巧已被证明是在与伊斯兰共和国
and his skills in negotiation have already proven to be a great asset
签署和平协议之前的最后几个小时内
in these final hours before the signing of the peace agreement
难能可贵的财富
with the Islamic Republic.
一旦哈桑夫人
Once Mrs. Hassan...
打搅了  总统阁下
Excuse me, Mr. President.
与伊斯兰共和国代表团
...and the IRK delegation...
去直升机场的车已经为您准备好了  就在楼下
Your car to the heliport is ready and waiting downstairs.
萨瓦洛夫总统的飞机到了没
Has, uh, President Suvarov's plane arrived yet?
应该再有二三十分钟就到肯尼迪机场了
It should be touching down at JFK within the next 20 to 30 minutes,
然后会有直升机送他去93号大道直升机场
and then he'll be choppered in to the 93rd Street Heliport.
谢谢你  艾伦
Thank you, Ellen.
通知他们我马上下去
Tell them I'll be down in a moment.
是  阁下
Yes, sir.
一旦哈桑夫人及伊斯兰共和国代表团
Once Mrs. Hassan and the IRK delegation
与泰勒总统解决了协议剩余的几个问题
have hashed out a few remaining points of protocol with President Taylor...
签署工作将如期进行
...the signing will commence as scheduled.
告诉我你们有鲍尔的线索了
Tell me you have a lead on Bauer.
抱歉  长官
I'm sorry, sir.
我们跟踪他到一栋邻近的大楼
We tracked him to an adjacent building,
但鲍尔还是设法逃出了包围圈
but Bauer managed to get out of the cordon,
还带走了记者梅瑞狄斯·里德
along with the reporter Meredith Reed.
他还杀了帕维尔
Also, he's killed Pavel.
我已从纽约警局那接过现场的管辖权
I've taken jurisdictional control over the scene from NYPD.
我们应该能够控制住局面  但是...
We should be able to keep this contained, but it...
如果鲍尔已将丹娜·沃什的证据交给媒体
it's not gonna matter if Bauer's already passed along the evidence
再怎么控制也没有意义了
he got from Dana Walsh to the press.
事情就要败露了
The story's going to come out.
不  不一定
No, not necessarily.
我们还是可以控制住的
We still might be able to manage this.
长官  我知道您说过
Look, sir, I- I know you've told me
承诺要把事情摆平
that you're committed to seeing this through,
但您现在还有机会抽身保持清白
but you can still extricate yourself from this mess.
还没有证据牵扯到您
There's no evidence of your involvement yet.
您还可以推迟新闻发布会
You can still delay the press announcement.
来不及了  杰森
It's too late for that, Jason.
白宫新闻发言人刚刚宣布了
The White House Press Secretary just announced
我在和平进程中的地位
my role in the peace process.
已无路可退了
There is no turning back.
还有件事该让您知道
And there's something else you should know.
鲍尔不仅仅是杀了帕维尔
Bauer didn't just kill Pavel.
而且是以开膛破肚的方式杀
He butchered him.
他对他一顿痛扁  还挖了他的内脏
He beat him savagely, and then he eviscerated him.
我认为鲍尔不仅仅是想
I don't think Bauer's just looking
曝光俄罗斯政府杀害哈桑的阴谋
to expose the Russians' involvement in the plot against Hassan.
这家伙是来报仇雪恨的
This guy's out for blood.
那你最好找到并阻止他  明白吗
Then you'd better find him and stop him, hadn't you?
是  长官
Yes, sir.
随时向我汇报
Keep me posted.
你要是不告诉我刚才在那发生什么了
I'm not going any further till you tell me
我就不走了
what happened back there.
你杀了那个人  对不对
You killed that man, didn't you?
里德女士  你现在有生命危险
Ms. Reed, your life is in danger.
你要是想活着度过难关
You want to get through this thing alive,
你就得严格照我说的做
you're gonna do exactly what I say.
明白吗
Do you understand?
杰克  我无法对你刚刚
Jack, I can't get a locate
用这个手机拨的号码进行定位
on the number you called from this phone.
被限制了
It's restricted.
我打算再逆向追踪一次
I'm gonna have to route a back trace.
你在这能做吗
Can you do it here?
不能  我需要我那里的设备
No. I need the equipment at my place.
你找出方位后马上给我电话
Get back to me as soon as you got a location.
-好的  -咱们走
- All right.  - Let's go.
你在找谁
Who is it you're looking for?
一个能告诉我所有涉案人员名单的人
Someone who can give me the names of everyone else involved.
等你找到他们你会怎么做
And what are you gonna do when you find them?
这与你无关
It doesn't concern you.
如果你不告诉我你在干嘛我怎么能相信你
How can I trust you if you don't tell me what you're doing?
因为想杀你的人不是我
Because I'm not the person who's trying to kill you.
我给你的那个视频文件
The video file that I gave you
是俄罗斯人合谋刺杀哈桑总统的唯一证据
is the only proof of the Russians' complicity president Hassan's assassination.
但这场阴谋并不仅仅牵扯到俄罗斯人
But the conspiracy doesn't end with the Russians.
我们政府内部有人
There are people within our own government
包括泰勒总统在内  正试图掩盖真相
that are trying cover this up, including President Taylor.
总统为什么要掩盖真相
Why would the president want this covered up?
因为她想继续与伊斯兰共和国签署和平协议
Because she's trying to keep the peace accord alive with the IRK.
她清楚如果让达莉亚·哈桑发觉
And she knows if Dalia Hassan finds out
俄罗斯人跟她丈夫的死脱不了干系
that the Russians had a hand in the death of her husband,
她将决不会签署协议
she'll never sign the agreement.
你想要我怎么样
What do you want from me?
如果我死了  我要你把事实公之于众
I need you to break the story in case I don't make it.
该还哈桑总统一个事实真相  你觉得呢
I think Presidt Hassan deserves that, don't you?
把你手机给我
Let me see your cell phone.
好
Okay.
等等  你干什么
Wait. What are you doing? I..
他们见过你和我在一起
They've seen you with me.
当局会开始监控
The authorities are going to start monitoring
你常用的通讯方式
your usual forms of communicaon.
你不能回家  不能回办公室
You can't go home, you can't go back to your office.
你有可以信任的同事吗
Is there anyone that you work with that you trust?
我的编辑盖里·克劳斯纳
Uh, my editor Gary Klausner.
你得试试把证据给他
You need to try and get him the evidence.
我就只能把你带到公用电话那里了
I can get you as far as a pay phone.
以后的事  你就只能靠自己了
After that, you're on your own.
很高兴我们能达成协议
I'm glad we were able to come to terms.
我也是
So am I.
总统阁下  感谢您的耐心
Thank you, Madam President, for your patience with me.
对谈判  我还是新手
I am still new to this.
您天生就是当领袖的料  达莉亚
You are a natural leader, Dalia,
而且您有位很棒的顾问  贾莫特部长
and you have a superb advisor in Minister Jamot.
感谢您的认可  总统阁下
I appreciate the endorsement, Madam President.
请原谅
Pardon me...
我的打扰
for interrupting.
我们刚刚结束
We were just finishing up.
达莉亚·哈桑
Dalia Hassan.
查尔斯·罗根
Charles Logan.
很荣幸终于见到了您  哈桑夫人
I'm honored to finally meet you, Mrs. Hassan.
我很崇敬您的丈夫
I was a great admirer of your husband.
请节哀
I'm so sorry for you loss.
谢谢您
Thank you.
泰勒总统告诉我
President Taylor tells me
您对于说服俄罗斯代表回到谈判桌前
you were instrumental in convincing the Russian delegates
有很大帮助
to stay at the negotiating table.
值此历史性的一刻
I'm honored to play even a small part
我为能尽微薄之力倍感荣幸
in such an historic event.
总统阁下  我能跟您谈谈吗
Madam President, may I have a few moments with you?
签署仪式上见
I'll see you at the signing.
你还没查清
You still haven't found out
罗根如何说服俄罗斯人继续谈判的
how Logan convinced the Russians to stay?
我调查过
I've investigated it,
可在代表团那边我一无所获
but I learned nothing from the delegates.
我可以让我们的情报部门调查一下
I can have our intelligence service look into it.
不用了  谢谢你  贾莫特
No. Thank you, Jamot.
我相信泰勒总统
I trust President Taylor.
我们必须相信她让罗根参与
We have to assume that if she involved Logan,
必定是有强有力的理由
it was for a good reason.
逮捕杰克·鲍尔的行动失败了
The operation to capture Jack Bauer was unsuccessful.
他带着从丹娜·沃什手上拿到的证据逃脱了
He got away, along with the evidence that he took from Dana Walsh.
你说过你已经控制了形势
You said you had the situation under control.
显然我是过于乐观了
Clearly, I was overly optimistic.
也是由于我的乐观
And in my optimism,
我忘了告诉您
I neglected to tell you
鲍尔跟一位记者
that Bauer made contact with a journalist.
梅瑞狄斯·里德取得了联络
Meredith Reed.
天哪
My God...
您必须马上给她的出版商打电话
You need to call her publisher right away.
宣布您对她所提供的任何证据事先都不知情
Deny any foreknowledge of whatever evidence she has,
并要求他们不要报道
and demand that they do not run the story.
你在建议我封住媒体的嘴吗
You're suggesting muzzling the press?
你忘了报道自由受到宪法保护吗
Have you forgotten that freedom of the press is Constitutionally protected?
我的天啊  您可是总统啊
You are the president, for God's sake.
您就说事关国家安全
Invoke national security.
告诉他们此事会成为战争的导火索
You tell them this story will start a war.
会让无辜者性命难保
Innocent lives will be lost.
谎言复谎言  谎言何其多
New lies to cover the old ones.
总统阁下  现在已经不是悲天悯人的时候了
The time has passed for hand wringing, Madam President.
如果您不动用白宫的力量
If you don't use the power of your office
阻止此事见报
to shut this story down,
损失的将不止是您的和平进程
your peace agreement won't be the only casualty.
不用我来告诉您
You don't need me to tell you the damage
对您诉诸刑事诉讼
that your criminal prosecution
将对这个国家产生的不良影响吧
will do to this country.
你在任时犯法  这个国家都挺过来了
This country survived your presidency.
但您在任期间就不一定了
But it won't survive yours.
我的总统之职是继任而来
Me- I inherited my presidency.
我从未像您这么受公众欢迎
I was never nearly as popular as you are.
而且大多数我所谓的罪行都没见报
And most of my alleged misdeeds never made the press.
可如果您将自己的罪过
But if you were to bare your sins
透露给将您推上总统宝座的人民...
to the people who put you in office...?
您是正义的导航明灯
You are a beacon of righteousness,
不止在美国人心中  也在全球民众心中
not only for Americans, but for the rest of the world.
您是位宁可让亲生女儿被捕
You are the president who had her own daughter arrested
都不愿让正义蒙羞的总统
rather than see justice go unserved.
你真是条蛊惑人心的毒蛇
You're a poison.
我真不该让你插手
I never should have let you do this.
恕我直言  总统阁下
With due respect, Madam President,
我是给过些建议
I- I gave recommendations,
我是做了些需要的安排
I made whatever arrangements needed to be made.
但一切决定都是您作出的
But every decision was yours.
咱们没法自欺欺人
Let's not pretend otherwise.
我研究您这个人
I've-I've studied you
好几年了  艾莉森
for a number of years, Allison.
我自负很会看人
I pride myself on being a good judge of character.
您是个聪明的女人
You're a smart woman.
您总知道需要做什么
You've always known what needed to be done
并且会下定决心去做
and were willing to do it.
所以我知道
Which is why I know
您会打给梅瑞狄斯·里德的出版商
you will call Meredith Reed's publisher
确保他不让那事见报
and make sure he kills the story.
我建议您现在就打
I would suggest you do it now.
您...
You, uh...
您有个签署仪式要准备
You have a signing ceremony to prepare for.
我得去见萨瓦洛夫总统了
And I need to go meet President Suvarov.
面部识别处理已启动
Facial Recognition Process Initiated
克罗伊
Chloe,
你得看看这个
you need to see this.
我刚接入了皮勒小队的现场视频
I just tapped into a live feed from Pillar's team.
发现这个人在百货公司对面
This guy was found strung up
一幢废弃的大楼里被吊起来并被开膛破肚
and sliced open in an abandoned building across from the department store.
他身上有俄罗斯证件
He's got Russian papers on him,
但我看不清  分辨率太低了
but I can't make 'em out; the rez is too low.
好像现场有人留了杆狙击枪
Looks like someone left a sniper rifle at the scene.
是什么口径的  调出来看看
What's the caliber? Bring it up.
上面标着是春田军工厂造  点308口径
They tagged it as a.308 Springfield.
那把就是杀死蕾妮的枪
That's the gun that killed Renee.
肯定就是那个狙击手
That's got to be the shooter.
是杰克干的  你还觉得能通过谈话阻止他吗
Jack did this, you're gonna be able to talk him down?
我必须一试
I gotta try.
皮勒和他的手下只想杀掉他
Pillar and his people are just gonna kill him,
我不能坐视不管
and I can't let that happen.
与百货公司获得的监控画面  82%匹配
Got a match from the department store security feed- 82%.
那就是杰克的帮手
That's the guy helping Jack?
对  詹姆斯·理查尔 前美军特种部队队员
Yeah, James Ricker- Ex-Green Beret, Special Ops.
他在杰克被召入反恐小组前
He served with Jack in the Gulf
曾在海湾战争时期与他一起服役
before Jack was enlisted by CTU.
只有一个问题
Just one problem.
上面说他死了
He's dead.
七年前  在巴士拉一次化工厂爆炸中身亡
It says he was killed in a chemical plant explosion in Basra seven years ago.
没错  那他肯定有个双胞胎兄弟
Yeah, well, then he must have a twin who was there
在杰克打反埋伏战时在场
when Jack reversed the ambush.
你最好回到自己的工作站去
You better go back to your station.
皮勒的眼线要起疑心了
Pillar's watchdog is getting suspicious.
阿洛
Arlo,
在车管所数据库里交叉比对理查尔的照片
cross-reference Ricker's photo with State DMV database.
他在城里生活肯定用了化名
He must be living under an alias in the city.
只要找到了理查尔  就能找到杰克
We find Ricker, we find Jack.
好
Okay.
喂
Yeah?
弄清他在哪了吗
You get the location?
你可没告诉我追踪的是罗根的电话   杰克
You didn't tell me that was Logan's phone that I was tracing, Jack.
有关系吗
Does it matter?
当然了
Yeah, it kind of does.
我认为你也清楚
I think you know it, too,
要不然你早就告诉我实话了
or else you would've been straight with me.
听着  解决一群俄罗斯间谍是一回事
Listen, taking out a bunch of Russian spooks is one thing,
但要动前总统  又是另外一回事了
moving on an ex-president, that's quite another.
你这是在玩火  哥们
That's a serious line you're crossing there, pal.
我很清楚我在干什么
I know exactly what I'm doing.
你到底告不告诉我他在哪
Are you gonna give me the location or not?
罗根在车上
Logan's in a vehicle.
他从联合国总部出来正向西行驶
He's moving west from the U.N.
我正在同步特勤局的部署网络
I'm syncing up with the Secret Service deployment grid.
我会把他的路线传到你的平板电脑上
I'll upload his route to your tablet.
稍等
Hold on.
正接收特勤局部署网之车辆路线文件
Receiving Datafile Secret Service Grid Map Vehicle Route
好了  我收到了
Okay, I've got it.
杰克  真希望你知道自己在干什么
Listen, Jack, I sure hope you know what you're doing,
因为你走上的是一条不归路
because this path you're on, there ain't no coming back from it.
我就没想过有退路
I wasn't planning on coming back.
你是对的  你为我所做的已经够多了
Look, you're right, you've already done more than I had right to ask for.
我要你现在开始清除和我一切的瓜葛
I want you to start erasing all your connections to me.
吉姆  感谢你为我所做的一切  再见
Jim... thanks for everything. Good-bye.
谢谢
Thank you.
这些就够了吗  我是否该去叫医生
Are you sure that's all you need? Should I call the doctor?
只是头疼而已
It's just a headache.
我没事  谢谢
I'm fine. Thank you.
-您找我吗  总统阁下  -是的  蒂姆
- You wanted to see me, Madame President? - Yes, Tim.
请坐
Please sit down.
还记得反恐组昨晚逮捕的那个记者吗
You remember the reporter CTU arrested last night?
记得  梅瑞狄斯·里德
Yes, uh, Meredith Reed.
据我所知
It has been brought to my attention
她打算发表一则关于奥马·哈桑之死的
that she intends to publish an unfounded story
毫无事实根据的报道
regarding Omar Hassan's murder.
她要写什么
What is she gonna be writing?
我需要你与联邦调查局取得联系
I need you to contact the FBI,
叫他们搜查星期日杂志社办公室
have them search the Sunday Magazine offices,
并截获她声称拥有的任何证据
and seize whatever evidence she purports to have.
我不是很明白
Um, I-I... I don't understand.
她宣称的一切都是假象
Her allegations are false,
但光这谣言就能破坏和谈进程
but the allegations alone could derail the peace process.
即便如此  总统阁下  您得清楚
Well, even so, Madam President, you have to be aware,
他们会控告您审查媒体
they'll accuse you of censoring the press.
蒂姆  我叫你来不是给我忠告的
Tim, I did not ask for your counsel.
我给你下的命令  我非常清楚
I know exactly what I'm ordering you to do,
你只管执行就是了
so please just do it.
遵命  总统阁下
Yes, ma'am.
下客接待处怎么走
Hey, drop-off and receiving?
往前走
Uh, yeah, straight ahead.
-就在那边  -谢谢
- Right there. - Thanks.
告诉道根让他来报道罗根的人物概评
Just make sure Duggan knows he's covering the Logan profile.
告诉他  我们会决定最后的署名
Tell him we'll work out the byline later.
主编办公室  我是克劳斯纳
Editor's desk. This is Klausner.
盖里  是我
Gary, it's me.
旁边有人吗
Look, a-are you alone?
说话方便吗
Can you speak freely?
方便
Yeah.
怎么了
Yeah, wh-what's going on?
我时间不多  我有一则报道的线索
I don't have a lot of time; I have a lead on a story.
-愿闻其详  -我有一份视频文件
- I'm listening. - I have a digital video recording
表明杀害哈桑总统的伊斯兰共和国恐怖份子
indicating that the IRK terrorists who killed Hassan
幕后的资助者和操纵者是俄罗斯间谍
were being funded and run by Russian operatives.
你确定是合法的吗
Uh, y-you sure it's legit?
你从哪弄来的
Where did you get it?
杰克·鲍尔那
From Jack Bauer.
鲍尔
Bauer?!
他是个逃犯
The man's a fugitive.
听着  盖里  现在说话真的很不安全
Look, Gary, it's really not safe for me to talk.
见面再说吧
I'll explain more when I see you.
你能和我见一面吗
Can you meet me?
当然可以
Sure, of course.
好  去那家咖啡让你反胃的餐馆
All right, that diner with the coffee you hate.
十五分钟内到
I can be there in, uh, 15 minutes.
好的  盖里  别告诉任何人
Okay. And, Gary, don't tell anyone.
好吗
All right?
我明白
I got it.
梅瑞狄斯  多加小心
Meredith... be safe.
嗯  你也要小心
Yeah. You, too.
完全没必要恐慌
There's no need to panic.
你知道他都对帕维尔干了什么吗
Do you know what he did to Pavel?
他遭受了毒打  然后像猪一样被开膛破肚
He was beaten savagely, gutted like a pig.
他手下全被枪杀了
His men shot dead.
我很遗憾
I'm... I'm sorry to hear that,
但你我彼此心知肚明...
but we both knew that, uh...
鲍尔不是一盏省油的灯
Bauer would be a difficult problem to solve.
你清楚他在干什么  对吧
You know what he's doing, don't you?
他在除掉任何与事件有牵连的人
He's eliminating everyone involved,
照他这样一路杀过来  找上我是迟早的事
working his way up- how long before he gets to me?
那不太可能
That's not going to happen.
你怎么就那么肯定
How can you be so sure?
因为是你自己对我说的
Because you told me yourself
你的手下嘴很严
your man would never talk,
如果是真的
and if that's true, then...
那么在你的核心集团之外就没人能指控你了
nobody outside of your inner circle can point the finger at you.
我向你保证
I promise you...
鲍尔是绝对不会知道的
Bauer's never going to know.
好消息是  鉴于他最近的行为
And on the upside, his recent activities
已给我们带来了一些好处
have given us a bit of an advantage.
什么好处
What advantage?
反恐组奉命已将处置他的方式升级为
CTU orders concerning him have been upgraded
"格杀勿论"
to "Shoot on sight."
但首先你得找到他
First you have to find him.
他们会找到他的  别担心
They're going to find him; don't worry.
他是不可能一直销声匿迹的
He can't... he can't stay under the radar forever.
有情况我会通知你
I'll keep you posted.
我们遭到袭击
We're under assault!
我们被困在了第四街的地下车道里
We are trapped in the 4th Street underpass.
我是L-1小组  请求立即支援
This is unit LEZ-1, requesting immediate backup.
两边的入口都堵住了  我们被围困了
Both entrances are blocked. We are boxed in.
那是杰克·鲍尔
Oh, that's... that's Jack Bauer.
一定是他
That's got to be.
没听到我说的吗
Did you hear what I said?!
那是杰克·鲍尔
That's Jack Bauer!
别干坐在那啊
Don't just sit there!
他是冲我来的
He's coming for me!
长官  待在车里
Sir, stay in the vehicle.
这是防弹车  玻璃也是防弹的
We're armored and the glass is bulletproof.
袭击我们的人戴着面具
The assailant is masked.
可能是杰克·鲍尔
It may be Jack Bauer.
-关门  保护车的安全  -关门
- Close the door! Secure the vehicle! - Close the door!
卧倒  总统阁下
Stay down, Mr. President!
杀了他
Kill him!
总统阁下  给我起来  否则我就地宰了你
Mr. President, get up, or I will kill you right here.
快走
Move!
我刚收到你的短讯
I just got your flash.
对理查尔的调查有什么发现吗
What'd you find out about Ricker?
你是对的
You were right.
车管所记录显示理查尔住在萨福克郡
DMV records show Ricker living in Suffolk County
化名西蒙·斯托克
under the name Simon Strocker.
我试图确认  发现他十八个月前搬走了
I tried to confirm, found out he moved from there 18 months ago,
但他留了新住址给邮局
but he left a forwarding address with the postal service-
他就住在本市苏荷区
it's right here in SoHo.
迪芬  出什么事了
Hey, Devon, what's going on?
皮勒的人请求外勤支援
Pillar's people are requesting backup for the team in the field.
你没听说吗
You didn't hear?
杰克·鲍尔刚刚绑架了查尔斯·罗根
Jack Bauer just kidnapped Charles Logan.
他怎么可能做得到
How the hell did he pull that off?
把查尔斯·罗根绑了
Charles Logan?
我得弄清他们在那屋里的勾当  跟我来
I need to hear what's going on in that room. Follow me.
你们还有多远
How far out are you?
正在接近地下车道
We're approaching the tunnel now.
特勤局是干什么吃的
How the hell did Secret Service let this happen?
鲍尔用催泪弹袭击了加长礼宾车
Bauer hit the town car with tear gas.
探员们全部中毒无力追赶
The agents were too incapacitated to pursue.
警局已经封锁了地下车道
PD's got the tunnel locked down.
我正在给你找地下车道图纸
I'm working on getting you schematics.
快点
Hurry up.
反恐组  让一下
CTU! Make a hole!
鲍尔挟持罗根总统去哪了
Where did Bauer take President Logan?
我不知道
I don't know.
你总不能什么也没看到吧
You must have seen something.
你告诉我  你看见什么了
Come on, tell me you saw something.
-抱歉  长官  -也没看到
- Sorry, sir.  - Nothing?
谁也没看见
No one saw anything.
伊登  他们走了地下维护通道
Eden, they went through an underground service gate.
我要通道的图纸
I need those schematics.
正在发送给你
Sending them to you now.
上
Go.
好的  科什  搜索过道
All right, Kirsch, take the corridor.
布朗  你到那下面去  埃姆斯  你跟我来
Brown, you're down there. Ames, you're with me.
记住  只要不对罗根总统构成直接威胁
Remember, unless it poses an immediate threat to President Logan,
你们一见到杰克就开枪击毙他
you shoot Bauer on sight, and you shoot to kill.
我们走
Let's go.
看着我
Look at me.
我叫你看着我
I said look at me!
我问你的你都得老实交代
You're going to tell me everything I want to know.
杰克  你误会了
Jack, you're making a mistake.
别给我装蒜说你跟这事没半点关系
Don't you even try and pretend you're not a part of this.
我找到了杀死蕾妮·沃克的人
I found the man who killed Renee Walker:
那个俄罗斯间谍  帕维尔·托卡列夫
the Russian operative Pavel Tokarev.
他接的最后一个电话就是你打的
The last call he got was from you.
我知道你一定认为是我  但你得听我解释
I know how it looks. You got to let me explain.
还解释什么
Explain what?
就是你派他来杀我的吗
That you sent for him to kill me?
是你派他来杀我的  对吧
You sent him to kill me, right?
对  见鬼  是我
Yes! Damn it, yes!
那你为什么还要杀蕾妮·沃克
Why did you take out a hit on Renee Walker?
那事跟我没关系
I had nothing to do with that.
那事之后我才卷进来的
I was brought in after that happened.
是谁拉你入伙的
Who brought you in?
泰勒总统要我帮她
President Taylor needed my help
说服俄罗斯人回到谈判桌前
to bring the Russians back to the table.
我打电话给我莫斯科的线人
I- I called my sources in Moscow.
他们告诉我他们政府里的人
They told me that people in their government
是暗杀哈桑的幕后主使
were behind Hassan's assassination.
我告诉俄罗斯代表团我有相关证据
I- I told the Russian delegation I had evidence of that fact
和所有涉案人员的名单
and the names of everybody involved.
我只是想让他们继续谈判罢了
It was just to keep them at the conference.
是什么证据
What evidence?!
根本没什么证据
It doesn't exist.
我赌上了一把
I was playing poker.
只是虚张声势  这招见效了
It was a bluff. It worked.
这让泰勒的和谈得以继续  但你...
It kept Taylor's peace agreement on the table, but you...
但你却决意要把这事搅黄了
You were determined to screw things up.
而且...
And to...
哎呦  息怒  杰克  别打了  我承认
Ow! Easy. Jack! Jack! Jack! I admit.
我承认  我参与了掩盖真相的阴谋
I admit, I was part of the cover-up,
但我并没有参与俄罗斯人的阴谋
but I'm not part of the Russian conspiracy.
恐怖袭击和你朋友的死都跟我都毫无关系
I had nothing to do with the terrorist attack or your friend's death.
我真不是干那种勾当的坏人
I- I... I'm... I'm not the bad guy here.
好啊  可你知道谁是
Okay, but you know who is.
你知道那个俄罗斯政府内部
You know the name of the person inside the Russian government
负责此事的人的名字  告诉我那个名字
who's giving the orders. I want that name.
-杰克  -快告诉我名字
- Jack...  - Give me the name!
-杰克  -在你脑袋开花之前
- Jack...  - You got five seconds
-你还有五秒钟时间考虑  -不 请别这样
- before I put a bullet through your head. - No! No! You don't have to do that.
-5...  -我说  我说
- Five...  - I'll tell you.
4  3...  是米哈伊尔·诺瓦科维奇
four... three... Mikhail Novakovich.
他是俄罗斯代表团的头
He's the head of the Russian delegation.
他从一开始就想让和平协议胎死腹中
He's been trying to kill the peace treaty from the start.
你在撒谎
You're lying.
不  不  我绝没撒谎  不要  不要啊
No! No! No! I'm not lying to you! No! No! No! No!
你不是从帕维尔的手机查到我的电话吗
You got my call from Pavel's phone.
你去查查之前的通话
You check the previous calls.
保准有一大堆诺瓦科维奇的电话
There's a dozen more from Novakovich.
听我的没错  他就是你要找的人
I'm telling you. He's the one you want.
闭嘴
Shut up!
再敢出声  我立马宰了你
Say another word, and I'll drop you right here.
上
Go!
跪下
Get on your knees.
别这样  求你了
Oh, no. Please.
不要杀我  杰克
Don't shoot me, Jack.
我要是想杀你  你早就挂了
If I was gonna kill you, you'd already be dead.
鲍尔刚才就在这里  找到他
Bauer was just here- find him!
总统阁下
Mr. President?
总统阁下  您没事吧  能听见我说话吗
Mr. President, are you okay? Can you hear me?
伊登  给我派个医疗小组到49号大街交叉口
Eden, I need a med unit at the 49th junction.
已经派出
On its way.
是抓到鲍尔了吗
Is it Bauer?
不  只发现了总统
No. It's the president.
他昏过去了
He's unconscious.
鲍尔跑了  我要你重新部署追捕
Bauer escaped. I'm gonna need you to redirect the pursuit.
我在这陪护总统
I'll stay with the president.
明白
Understood.
他们还是可能会抓到他
They still might catch up to him.
至少现在还没  有理查尔的档案了吗
They haven't yet. Do you have Ricker's file?
有  包括目前的住址
Yeah, including his current address.
我马上传你
I'm sending it to you now.
你准备怎么处理这事
How are you planning to handle this?
为了不让皮勒知道
We can't send any tactical units
我们又不能派任何战术小组去找他
to pick this guy up without Pillar finding out about it.
我不会用他们
I'm not using any of them.
那你打算派谁去
Then who are you going to get?
我们的所有探员都出任务了
All of our agents are fully deployed in the field.
无人可调遣了
There's nobody to send.
还有一个人
There's one.
奥布赖恩女士
Ms. O'Brian?
Ms. O'Brian?!
我刚看到总部的通知
I just saw the flash from division.
他们同意了你的请求
They approved your request
释放奥迪斯探员交你监管
to release Agent Ortiz into your custody?
对  我还有急事  失陪
Yeah, I'm in a hurry, so...
你知道你在干什么吗
What do you think you're doing?
他是名因拒不配合被联邦法院起诉的目击证人
He's a non-cooperative witness who is facing federal charges.
或许你没发现
In case you haven't noticed,
我仍负责联合国总部的安全
I'm still in charge of UN Security,
而你占用了我的所有可调配资源
and you've taken away all my resources.
而且这本来就不是你管的
And not that it's any of your business,
而是奥迪斯探员计划了整个联合国的安全事宜
but Agent Ortiz designed the entire UN operation.
还有不到两小时就要进行签署仪式了
The signing is in less than two hours.
他在外勤任务中的作用至关重要
His assistance in the field is vital.
我得让皮勒批准此事才行
I'm going to have to clear this with Pillar.
悉听尊便   但我看你还有更大的麻烦要处理
Do what you want, but to me, you have bigger problems,
比如先去找到杰克·鲍尔
like not finding Jack Bauer.
你是梅瑞狄斯吗
Are you Meredith?
是的
Yes.
有个叫盖里·克劳斯纳的打电话找你
There's a Gary Klausner on the phone for you.
-电话在收银台的边上  -谢谢
- It's up by the cashier. - Thank you.
谢谢
Thanks.
你在哪
Where are you?
梅瑞狄斯  联调局来人了
Meredith, the FBI is here.
我能离开之前他们就到了
Showed up before I could leave.
他们在找你  盘问包括我在内的所有人
They're looking for you,  questioning everyone, including me.
你什么都没说  对吗
You didn't tell them anything, did you?
当然没有了
Of course not.
但他们有总统签署的行政命令
But they've got an executive order from the president.
他们说你手上的东西
They say you're in possession of materials
对国家安全构成了威胁
that pose a national security risk.
这是在掩盖真相  盖里
It's a cover-up, Gary.
白宫想要禁止此事见报
The White House is trying to suppress the story.
你不能让他们得逞
You can't let them.
听着  在我们渡过这一关前
Look, until we clear this up,
你得保护好证据
you have to protect that evidence.
我告诉他们我已经跟你撇清关系了
I told them I haven't had any contact with you,
但据我所知  他们正在追踪这个电话
but for all I know, they're tracing this call.
你最好马上离开那里
You better get the hell out of there.
去哪里
And go where?
我们说过不要跟外界联系
We said no communication outside of our presence.
我只是在取消一个约会
I- I I'm canceling an appointment.
盖里  他们想掩盖真相
Gary, they're going to bury the truth.
有我在他们就休想
Not if I can help it.
我会设法和司法部的爱德·桑普森联系
I'll try to put a call into Ed Sampson  at the Justice Department,
但在那之前  躲起来  现在赶紧离开
but until then, lay low. Now go.
好的
Okay.
-我们走  -去哪
- Let's go. - Where are we going?
我得去一趟联合国总部
I have to go to the U.N.,
总部已准许暂时释放你并由我监管
and division has given you a temporary furlough into my custody.
因为你之前是联合国的安保工作的总指挥
Since you had earlier command of UN security,
协调好签署仪式的安保方案及部署工作
coordinating protocols and deployment for the signing ceremony.
皮勒同意了吗
And Pillar's okay with this?
我依然是临时主管
I'm still provisional Director of Operations.
我不需要获得他的批准
I don't need his consent.
那么你是跟我来
So, are you coming,
还是更愿意在这等候对你的联邦诉讼
or would you rather wait here for your federal prosecution?
我们走
Let's go.
他就交给我了
I'll take him from here.
-你要告诉我到底是怎么回事吗  -是的
- You want to tell me what's really going on? - Yeah.
你说的没错  确实有人帮杰克
You were right about Jack. He is working with somebody.
詹姆斯·理查尔  前中情局情报特工
It's James Ricker, ex-CIA Op.
我们已经找到他的在梅瑟大街的住所了
We found him living at a place on Mercer Street
他的化名叫西蒙·斯托克
under the alias Simon Strocker.
或许他还在为政府工作
Maybe he's still with the company.
不  我向中情局确认过了  他被列为已死亡
No. I checked with Langley. He was listed as deceased.
他更有可能在以军火或情报交易
More than likely, he's gone into business for himself,
为自己牟利  无论怎样
dealing arms or intel. In any case,
我们找到他的话他一定不会高兴的
he's not going to be happy we tracked him down.
等等  你为什么要告诉我这些
Wait a second. Why are you telling me this?
我要你去跟他谈谈
I need you to talk to him.
让他说出杰克的下落
Get him to tell us where Jack is.
你能处理好吗  或者你还没想好该站哪边
Are you good with that, or have you still not taken sides?
我跟你一样想让真相大白于天下  算上我
I want to expose this cover-up as much as you. I'm in.
好  登记表上会显示你跟我一同去了联合国
Good. Log sheets will show you accompanying me to the UN.
我找了一辆车在门口等你
I've secured you a separate vehicle waiting at the gate.
有更多关于杰克的消息吗  他重新露面了吗
Is there any more intel on Jack? Has he resurfaced again?
是的  可以那么说
Yeah, you could say that.
阁下  我刚收到消息
Sir, I just received word.
萨瓦洛夫总统的专机已抵达肯尼迪机场
President Suvarov's plane has touched down at Kennedy Airport.
告诉伊万把车开来
Tell Ivan to bring the car around.
我要在联合国总部等候总统大驾
I want to be at the UN when the president arrives.
是的  长官
我五分钟内到前门
诺瓦科维奇在哪
Where's Novakovich?
-我不会再问第二遍  -十一楼
- I'm not going to ask you again. - 11th.
十一楼  1170套房内
11th floor, suite 1170.
我怎么上去
How do I get up there?
停车场里有安全电梯
Secure elevator inside of garage.
-你的门卡在哪  -我没有门卡
- Where's your keycard? - I don't have one.
你的门卡在哪
Where is your keycard?
我真的没有  我发誓
I don't have one, I swear.
他的贴身保镖在电梯那  他们有门卡
His personal guards have them at elevator.
-有多少人  -两人
- How many? - Two.
房间外一名  里面有两名
One outside the suite, two inside.
还有一名守在电梯那
Another by elevator.
还有哪里有  还有吗
Where else? Where else?!
就这些  我就知道这么多了
That's all. That's all I know.
你真需要那么多武器吗
Do you really need an arsenal?
有备无患
Better to have it than to not.
毕竟理查尔是个训练有素的杀手
Besides, Ricker's a trained killer.
他肯定身经百战才得以隐姓埋名
He's gone to a lot of trouble to stay off the grid.
有道理
Fair enough.
我还得考虑到万一杰克和他在一起呢
I also have to consider the possibility that Jack's with him.
听着  克罗伊
Listen, Chloe,
从你告诉我他对罗根的所作所为后
I can't be worried about Jack anymore,
我不能再考虑杰克的安全了
not after what you told me he did to Logan.
显然  罗根也参与了此次阴谋
Obviously, Logan's part of the conspiracy.
他手持自动步枪暴力突袭了满是上班族的隧道
He terrorized a tunnel full of commuters with automatic weapon fire.
他居然对特勤组探员开枪
He shot Secret Service agents.
他只是打伤了他们
He shot to wound.
他根本不在乎  他在乎的只是复仇
He's careless, and he only cares about revenge.
你觉得他还是你认识的那个人吗
Does that sound like the man you know?
还是你想保护的那个人吗
Like the man you're trying to save?
这一切只是为了揭穿俄罗斯人掩盖真相的阴谋
This is about exposing the Russians' cover-up.
不是为了杰克
It's not about Jack.
你确定吗
Are you sure about that?
因为如果杰克在那
Because if Jack's there,
他如果有任何拘捕的举动
and he makes any move other than complete surrender...
我会把他放倒的
I'm putting him down.
你还想要我去吗
You still want me to go?
我别无选择
I don't really have a choice.
无论发生什么  打电话到联合国找我
Whatever happens, call me at the U.N.
知道了
You got it.
在签署仪式之前  您可以直接进入会场
You'll approach the rostrum immediately prior to the signing ceremony,
就坐在这  三号位置  您母亲身边
and take a seat here in position three, next to your mother.
但这合适吗
But is that appropriate?
我虽然是她的女儿
I may be her daughter,
但我在政府中没有任何正式职位
but I don't have any official role in government.
打扰下  哈桑女士
Excuse me. Ms. Hassan,
您父亲的安全线路上有一个电话
there's a call on your father's secure line-
有位女士要求和您的母亲通话
a woman demanding to speak with your mother.
她正在开会
She's in a meeting.
我说了  不过她执意要见您母亲
That's what I said, but this woman is quite insistent.
她是谁
Who is she?
她不愿说
She won't say.
我这边汇报完毕了  哈桑女士
We're done, Ms. Hassan.
等候区见
I'll see you in the staging area.
谢谢
Thank you.
二号线
Line two.
谢谢
Thank you.
你好  哪位
Hello. Who is this?
是凯拉吗
Is this Kayla?
你是谁
Who are you?
抱歉...
Sorry, um...
我叫梅瑞狄斯·里德
my name is Meredith Reed.
我需要跟你母亲通话
I need to speak to your mother.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
你居然有脸往这里打电话
What do you think you're doing calling here?
我知道你和你母亲现在
I- I know I'm the last person
最不愿听到的就是我的声音
that either of you wants to talk to right now...
知道就好  我要挂了
You're right. I'm hanging up now.
不  求求你
No, please, please,
在你母亲同泰勒总统签署协议前
your mother needs to hear what I have to say
一定要听听我说的
before she signs the agreement with President Taylor.
什么事这么重要
What is it that is so important?
抱歉  我必须直接同你母亲讲
I- I'm sorry, I need to speak to your mother directly.
你给我母亲带来的伤害还不够吗
Haven't you caused my mother enough pain?
离我们远点
Leave us alone!
此事事关谋杀你父亲的真凶
It's about the people who really murdered your father.
你说什么
What are you talking about?
我们知道凶手是谁
We know who was responsible.
但你不知道
What you don't know is,
这些凶手听命于一群俄罗斯间谍
those people were working under the orders of Russian agents.
什么
What?!
-喂  -你母亲开会回来时
- Hello?  - When your mother gets back from her meetings,
让她打我这个号码  请记一下
have her call me at this number- can you take this down?
说吧
Go ahead.
212-555-0121
It's 212-555-0121.
那时我会跟她把一切解释清楚的
I'll explain everything to her then.
等一下
Wait...!
梅瑞狄斯·里德
Meredith Reed?
联邦调查局   把手举起来
FBI. Get your hands where we can see 'em.
怎么回事
What is this?
等一下
Wait. Wait.
你们无权拿走它
You have no right to take that.
我什么坏事也没做
I- I haven't done anything wrong.
这是怎么回事
What is this?
你被逮捕了
You're under arrest.
-我什么坏事也没做  -我们走
- I - I've done nothing wrong. - Let's go.
我什么坏事也没做
I've done nothing wrong!
什么事
Yes?
伍兹先生来了  总统阁下
Mr. Woods, ma'am.
我刚从联邦调查局那得到消息
I've just received word from the FBI.
里德已经被捕
Reed is in custody,
他们在她身上搜出了一张数据卡
and they've secured a data card they found on her.
除了我谁都不许看卡里的内容
No one sees what's on it but me.
明白
Understood.
长官  下面交给我们了
Sir, we'll take it from here.
不行  我要陪他一起去医院
No, you won't - I'm riding with him to the hospital.
回避一下
Give him some space.
诺瓦..诺瓦科维..
Nova... Novakov...
诺瓦..
Nova...
诺瓦科维奇
Novakovich.
鲍尔知道了
Bauer knows.
快去警告诺瓦科维奇  鲍尔去找他了
Warn Novakovich Bauer's coming after him.
长官  我们得走了
Sir, we gotta get going.
还不行  在这里把他照顾好就是了
Not yet. Just do what you can for him here.
明白
Understood.
喂
Yes?
诺瓦科维奇先生吗
Mr. Novakovich?
喂  喂
Hello? Hello?
我是伯科夫
It's Berkov.
我们遭到了袭击
We've been attacked.
是鲍尔干的
It was Bauer.
诺瓦科维奇在哪
Where's Novakovich?
他死了
He's dead.
所有人都死了
Everyone is dead.
伯科夫  诺瓦科维奇对鲍尔说过什么吗
Berkov, did Novakovich say anything to Bauer?
我需要辆救护车
I need an ambulance.
赶快回答我的问题
Just answer my question.
诺瓦科维奇跟鲍尔说什么了
What did Novakovich say to Bauer?
什么也没说  鲍尔进来就开枪
Nothing. Bauer just came in shooting.
不过他在流血
But he was bleeding.
估计是被一个保镖刺伤的
I think he was wounded by one of the guards.
好吧  别乱动  救护车马上就到
All right, sit tight; an ambulance is on the way.
走开
Go.
诺瓦科维奇死了
Novakovich is dead.
鲍尔把他杀了  还有他全部手下
Bauer killed him, killed all of his men...
我不知道诺瓦科维奇是否跟鲍尔说过什么
I don't know if Novakovich said anything to Bauer.
喂
Yes?
我是查尔斯·罗根
Charles Logan.
我本以为你会来直升机场接我
I was under the impression you were going to be at the heliport for my arrival.
这个嘛
Yes, well...
我这边遇到点麻烦
...I ran into some trouble.
恐怕是坏消息
I'm afraid I have bad news.
看起来米哈伊尔·诺瓦科维奇
It appears that Mikhail Novakovich
刚被杰克·鲍尔给杀了
was just murdered by Jack Bauer.
-什么  -是的
- What?! - Yeah,
鲍尔了解到诺瓦科维奇负责指挥并协调
and Bauer learned that Novakovich was responsible for ordering and...
对奥马·哈桑的刺杀行动
coordinating Omar Hassan's assassination,
以及萨米尔的那些勾当
as well as the rest of Samir's activities.
他从何处得知的
Where would he get that idea?
从我这里
From me.
那疯子要杀了我  尤里
The lunatic was gonna kill me, Yuri.
你还能指望我说什么
What can I say?
我想这也算是弃车保帅啊
Think of it as sacrificing a rook for a king.
那么  鲍尔还不知道
Then Bauer has no idea
诺瓦科维奇是遵从我的命令行事的  对吗
that Novakovich was operating under my orders?
是的
None.
据目击者所讲
Uh, according to a witness,
米哈伊尔就算想供你出来  都没机会
Mikhail didn't have a chance to give you up, even he wanted to.
对鲍尔来说
As far as Bauer is concerned...
做了诺瓦科维奇就完事了
the trail ended with Novakovich.
而且全城各执法部门都在搜捕他
And he's being hunted by every law enforcement agency in the city.
而且我听说他受伤了
And I've-I've heard that, uh...he's been wounded.
受伤的猛兽才是最可怕的
There is nothing more dangerous than a wounded animal.
如果你这么担心鲍尔的话
Look, if you're so worried about Bauer,
就不应该下令杀掉蕾妮·沃克
you never should have given the order to kill Renee Walker.
就是这事捅了马蜂窝
That's what stirred up the hornet's nest.
如果我早知道你会发现我们的行动
If I had known that you were going to find out about our activities
并且用你所获得的情报
and use that information
来要挟我签署泰勒的和平协议的话
to blackmail me into signing Taylor's peace agreement,
我根本就不会动那个女人
I wouldn't have bothered with the woman.
木已成舟了  尤里
Water under the bridge, Yuri.
我当时需要一个重返政坛的机会
I needed an opportunity to put myself back in the game.
很抱歉只能以牺牲你为代价了
I'm sorry that it has come at your expense.
你不会同一个想东山再起的老朋友计较这些的吧
You wouldn't begrudge an old friend his second chance in the sun.
那好吧
All right, then.
我会在联合国总部跟你会面
I will- I will meet you at the United Nations...
我会尽快赶到
as soon as I can.